# **Zainudin Noori**

# **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

zainudinnory@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

## **SUMMARY**

A full-stack web developer with a passion for creating innovative and engaging web experiences, Zainudin Noori is committed to pushing the boundaries of technologies to create powerful and effective solutions. With a deep understanding of the latest web technologies and a keen eye for more learning. His unique combination of technical skills, creative vision, and collaborative spirit make him an ideal candidate for any web development team.

## **SKILLS**

Front-End: JavaScript, Vue.js, Ajax, jQuery, JSON, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, and Tailwind CSS.

Back-End: PHP, Laravel, Livewire, ASP.net MVC, Inertia.js, PostgreSQL, and MySQL.

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Jira and Trello.

Professional: Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork, Mentoring, Agile, Scrum and project management.

Cloud Servers & OS: AWS, Digital Ocean, Cloudflare, Linux, and Windows Server.

Languages: Dari/Persian (Native), Pashto (Native), English (Professional), Hindi/Urdu (Fluent)

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### HIGHLIGHTED PERSONAL PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer

Remote

2021 - Present

Glist — Beauty Professionals list services as freelancers and Clients search & book services based on availability, price, review, locations, etc.

Built with: (PHP, Laravel, Livewire, Stripe, Java script, Vue.js, Firebase, Cron jobs)

BulBul – Bulbul is the first and only mobile application built to deliver premium-quality audiobooks for its users.

• Built with: (PHP, Laravel, Inertia.js, Vue.js, Firebase)

Server Monitor App — Check and monitor your Websites/Servers and get notified when it is down.

Built with: (PHP, Laravel, ¡Query, Ajax, Shell Scripting, Automation tools, Firebase)

#### **INTELLECTUAL APPLICATIONS & PRODUCTS**

Remote

#### Full Stack Web Developer

03, 2020 - Present

- Develop and deploy various customized web applications which included data reporting, data management, data visualization, user management, restful API development, and online payment implementations.
- Maintained security, performance and availability of the websites.

#### **NETLINKS LTD**

Kabul, Afghanistan

#### Web Developer & System Administrator

07,2017 - 03,2020

- Developed web-based applications using variety of technologies including Angular, Laravel, and Vue.js,
- Maintained backup servers, generated reports, ensured systems security, performance, uptime and availability.

## **EDUCATION**

## APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATIONS

2016 - 2017

#### Diploma in .Net. Full Time

- Microsoft Completion certificate (C#)
- Acquired strong programming and system analysis skills

#### BANGALORE UNIVERSITY

06, 2014 - 07, 2017

## **Bachelor of Computer Applications, Software Development**

- First Class Distinction (CGPA: 7.64)
- Developed the Library management portal for the College used by more than 2000 students and Lecturers.